http://www.stbarbe-museum.org.uk/about-us/privacy-policy.php

Contact
Museums & CollectionsArt GalleryKing Research RoomVisitor Information PointNewsGift ShopRoom HireLook Inside
CalendarCurrent ExhibitionExhibition ReviewsFuture ExhibitionsPast ExhibitionsArt GalleryFriends EventsFamilyAdult Learning
Opening TimesTicket PricesGetting HereEating & DrinkingDisability & Access
About St BarbeThe TeamTrusteesSt Barbe and Art GalleryPrivacy PolicyVacancies
Learning and EngagementSchools Activities
Get InvolvedDonateInspire FundFriendsPatronsLeaving A LegacyBusiness OpportunitiesVolunteerThank You
Contact
Museums & CollectionsArt GalleryKing Research RoomVisitor Information PointNewsGift ShopRoom HireLook Inside
CalendarCurrent ExhibitionExhibition ReviewsFuture ExhibitionsPast ExhibitionsArt GalleryFriends EventsFamilyAdult Learning
Opening TimesTicket PricesGetting HereEating & DrinkingDisability & Access
About St BarbeThe TeamTrusteesSt Barbe and Art GalleryPrivacy PolicyVacancies
Learning and EngagementSchools Activities
Get InvolvedDonateInspire FundFriendsPatronsLeaving A LegacyBusiness OpportunitiesVolunteerThank You
Privacy Notice
St Barbe Museum and Art Gallery respects your privacy.
The information we collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted to St Barbe Museum and Art Gallery.
The way we use information
We use the personal information you give us as a research tool to develop the content of the Museum’s websites, to develop our understanding of our visitors and to determine how best to serve them.
We may use the information to provide you with details of the Museum’s services and for this reason each communication that asks for data gives you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such data.
We use return email addresses to answer the emails we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We will not send your data to third parties and we will not send data to areas where an adequate data protection policy is not in place.
Information collected automatically
The website collects some anonymous information about you automatically as you move through the site. This information is used to help us monitor how you and other visitors use the site, allowing us to provide an improved service throughout the site. The information collected automatically does not, however, contain anything that can identify you personally.
Use of cookies
Some sections of this website use cookies. Cookies are small, text-only strings of data which store information on the hard drive of your local computer or mobile device. Some cookies store data just for the time you are on the site. These are called session cookies and are not stored on your computer after you have left the site.
These cookies do not contain any personal data about you individually. They are there to provide you with better information tailored to your individual needs. Most internet browsers are pre-set to accept cookies but if you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you when they are being used.
When you visit the St Barbe Museum website, if your browser is using the standard settings and it is accepting cookies, you are giving consent for cookies on the St Barbe site to be stored on your computer. If you do not wish for this to happen, you can disable them in the settings of your browser.
This has to be done on each different browser you use. For more information about how to disable cookies in different browsers, visit Aboutcookies.org
What type of cookies?
We use Google Analytics to collect information about site usage and performance. This helps us better understand our users and their needs so that we can continue to improve the services we provide. We also use this information to report to funders such as the Heritage Lottery Fund and Arts Council England. The analytics cookies collect information such as the number of visits to the site, pages visited and international traffic. This information is anonymous and cannot be used to identify you personally.
Our commitment to data security
To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How you can access or correct your information
You can access all your personal identifiable information that we collect by contacting the Marketing and Development Manager at marketing@stbarbe-museum.org.uk .
Your rights
You can ask us at any time to provide you with a copy of the information we hold about you, including where and how we obtained it, why we are keeping it and what we are using it for. This is called a "subject access request" and you can make one by contacting the Data Protection Officer by emailing: marketing@stbarbe-museum.org.uk
or writing to:
Data Protection Officer (Marketing and Development)
St Barbe Museum and Art Gallery
New St,
Lymington,
SO41 9BH
We may need to ask you to provide copies of identity documents to make sure that we are releasing your information to the right person.
If you no longer want to hear about our news, events, campaigns or fundraising activities, you can ask us to stop contacting you by calling 01590 676969 or writing to us at the above address.
We may not be able to completely delete all of your information from our systems, as there are some records we must keep for legal and regulatory requirements. These include Gift Aid records and sales records.
If you have a comment, concern or complaint about the way your personal information has been used, please let us know so that we can make things right.
About St Barbe
Telling the story of Lymington and the New Forest coast HERE
Friends Events
Browse upcoming friends events HERE
Thank You
For supporting St Barbe Museum HERE
St Barbe Museum and Art Gallery, New Street, Lymington, Hampshire, SO41 9BH
